{
    "subject": "resource/Canada_Place",
    "predicate": "ontology/cost",
    "object": "4.0E8",
    "human_readable": "The cost of Canada Place is $40,000,000.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7875248193740845,
            "question": "What is the cost of Canada Place?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7488882541656494,
            "question": "Is there a significant cost associated with Canada Place?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5496619343757629,
            "question": "How much did it cost to build Canada Place?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49632492661476135,
            "question": "What is the estimated value of Canada Place today?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4957555830478668,
            "question": "What is the monetary worth of Canada Place?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46647900342941284,
            "question": "Is Canada Place an expensive building?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46048593521118164,
            "question": "Does the price of Canada Place reflect its size or purpose?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4325796067714691,
            "question": "Can you provide the financial value of Canada Place?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39858564734458923,
            "question": "How much money was invested in constructing Canada Place?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36749348044395447,
            "question": "What price tag was attached to Canada Place?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The cost of Canada Place is $40,000,000.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3091_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How much money was invested in constructing Canada Place?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3091_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you provide the financial value of Canada Place?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3091_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does the price of Canada Place reflect its size or purpose?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3091_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3091_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3091_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3091_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3091_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3091_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3091_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3091_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3091_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3091_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3091_82.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided text states that the federal government previously committed $50,000 for Canada Place. There is no mention of a total cost of $40,000,000.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents do not provide any specific information about the cost of Canada Place being $40,000,000. The document related to Canada Place discusses a federal government commitment of $50,000 and mentions the need for additional funds due to cost overruns but does not specify an exact total cost of $40,000,000."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}